[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_GatherAllies_Sun_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need a new home.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I have traveled extensively in my time on Aeternum, but I've only ever felt safe in Ebonscale Reach.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_GatherAllies_Sun_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"They've taken Ebonscale?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I hope not. Surely, the Empress was prepared and she and her loyal warriors remain safe… but this area seems to have fallen.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_GatherAllies_Samir_TalkTo_00",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll find him. Don't worry.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Good. I will look for Constance and Walker. We'll all meet up with you shortly.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_GatherAllies_Wayne_TalkTo_00",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That means she finished them off.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "At least there's some good news in all this mess.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_GatherAllies_Grace_TalkTo_00",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We're going to Ebonscale.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ah, then Sun will be leading the Wardens west, will she? Hm. Now where will fortune be leading Grace O'Malley, you think?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_GatherAllies_Grace_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"They're safe.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Good. I thought all was lost for a minute there. What I want to know is how the the red-eyed rotters knew we were coming.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_GatherAllies_Grace_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"If I'm there, you won't be safe.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Now why would you go and say a thing like that? You've been the savior at every turn!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_MeetWiseman_Qi_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I need your help.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, you do. I can sense from here the discord in your thoughts, and your... unwelcome observer.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_MeetWiseman_Qi_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "Your mind and body and spirit are all connected. Like the gongs, if one is in disharmony, then all will fall into discord.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_MeetWiseman_Qi_TalkTo_03",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How can I stop it?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "You must learn to balance the vital essences of your being. Focus them through an inner calm: your heartbeat, as though music.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_CreateRefuge_Yash_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "This doesn't feel right. I do not trust in Grace's choice of shelter. It feels like we are very much exposed here.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_CreateRefuge_Yash_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You should help too.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I should, yes. I know. I just need a little more time to center myself and get my bearings. Come and speak with me later.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_InspireAllies_Grace_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "But I have doubts. Not like we're coming off a lucky streak! And the mood around here… I've attended livelier funerals.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_InspireAllies_Yash_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need to rekindle the feeling.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "With this? No offense, but the stitching is rough. And the scorch marks… it's hard not to think of…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_CreateIncense_Zhou_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "I would be stronger. But ever I hear these… whispers. I am doing everything I can to resist. My options are fleeting.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_CreateIncense_Sun_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I certainly mean to try.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Then you choose to shoulder a burden the weight of which you are wholly ignorant. That is no insult. I am impressed.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_FightLiang_Sun_TalkTo_00",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I trust fully in your skills.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "And I do appreciate that. Are you ready to begin? The rest falls to you.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_FightLiang_Sun_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do we do now?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I'm sorry. I am... overcome. It has been so long. What we have accomplished is miraculous, but there is a long road ahead.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_ReuniteFamily_Liang_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"At least three. Here they are.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I see… I feel like there were far more than that. And yet…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_ReuniteFamily_Sun_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Will his mind recover, too?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Slowly, I suspect. To be trapped inside that monstrous form for so long… it will take time to recover his faculties.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_ReuniteFamily_Grace_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"To be reunited with his mother.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I know, quite an honor! I've met Lords and Ladies, and even a Queen, but never an Empress.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_ReuniteFamily_Sun_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That's understandable.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I simply want to express my deepest gratitude. Despite the darkness we endured getting here, I am inspired.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_ReuniteFamily_Grace_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What happened?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "The Prince and I came along expecting to hike up to the monastery, and we ran right into them!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_ReuniteFamily_Zhou_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I assure you, this is your son.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I will not be fooled by some imposter! Liang remains an abomination, but I will remedy his affliction in my own way.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_DeliverPoem_Liang_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I found it washed ashore.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Oh! This was her favorite poem by Du Fu… \"Over Kuizhou's lonely wall, the setting sun slants...\"",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99F_DeliverPoem_Sun_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You should stay with him.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "It is not an easy decision, but it is the right thing for me to do.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
